https://www.qbalance.com/privacy-policy/

(800) 216-0763
0 Items Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://www.qbalance.com and Qbalance and governs data collection and usage.  For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Qbalance include https://www.qbalance.com and Qbalance. The Qbalance website is a QuickBooks Support site. By using the Qbalance website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationIn order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Qbalance may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:First and Last NameMailing AddressE-mail AddressPhone NumberEmployerIf you purchase Qbalance’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information, This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Qbalance’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.  However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Use of your Personal InformationQbalance collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.Qbalance may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Qbalance and its affiliates.Sharing Information with Third PartiesQbalance does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.Qbalance may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Qbalance, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Qbalance may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Qbalance or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Qbalance; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Qbalance, or the public.Automatically Collected InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Qbalance. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Qbalance website.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable informationSecurity of your Personal InformationQbalance secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Qbalance uses the following methods for this purpose:SSL ProtocolWhen personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.E-mail CommunicationsFrom time to time, Qbalance may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.Changes to this StatementQbalance reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.Contact InformationQbalance welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Qbalance has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Qbalance at:6 Robert Dr, Lebanon, New Jersey 08833Email Address:support@qbalance.comTelephone number:(800) 216-0763Effective as of October 25, 2019Privacy Policy was last modified:
October 25th, 2019 by Barrett Makrecky
